

ARRASYID FADEL **FATONSYAH**

Fullstack Developer

Kudus, Central Java

- aff.anton20@gmail.com
- 089-635-164-141
- <u>@arrasyidff-github</u>
- arrasyid-fadel-fatonsyahlinkedin
- arfafa-web

ABOUT ME

My name is Arrasyid Fadel Fatonsyah, I'm 25 years old. I'm a Backend Developer, but I'm also interested in the Frontend side. For most of my projects, I am responsible for the backend side. I am also always enthusiastic about new things with what I do, and I can contribute well as a team and individually.

VUE

CSS • SCSS

REACT

JOUERY

TAILWIND

SKILLS

- JAVASCRIPT
- NODE.JS
- EXPRESS.JS
- SEQUELIZE
- PHP
- LARAVEL
- MYSQL
- POSTGRESQL
- MONGODB
- RESTFULL API

PORTFOLIO

Web Portfolio

https://arfafa.netlify.app/

This website is designed to provide a comprehensive overview of my background, skills, experience, and projects I have worked on. The main purpose of this website is to make it easier for you to find out more about me and my work through an attractive and informative display

School Static Web

https://school-mb.web.app/ Create a static website with a school theme and add information from the school

WORK EXPERIENCE

BACKEND DEVELOPER

PT. INOSOFT TRANS SISTEM

November 2021 - Now

Add, change, and fix features as requested. And also help the team to solve existing problems so that the web application can work according to its function

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

CV. AKASA TECH DWIJAYA BALI

April 2021 - Nov 2021

Add, change, and fix features as requested. And also help the team to solve existing problems so that the web application can work according to its function

EDUCATION

HACKTIV8 INDONESIA

FULLSTACK IMMERSIVE / FULLSTACK JAVASCRIPT 9/2021 - 1/2022

Learn new things and complete assignments every day with tight deadlines. Also, create several projects with the things learned previously

ITB STIKOM BALL

SISTEM INFORMASI

08/2018 - 09/2020 (Unfinished - 4th Semester) Decided not to continue studying during Covid. And decided to continue learning at the Hacktiv8 Indonesia Bootcamp, so I can start working straight away